BU Records: Chancellor's Office (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1980-1988, undated, Bulk: 1981-1985
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
BU Records: Chancellor's Office (Abner Vernon McCall)
Inclusive: 1980-1988, undated, Bulk: 1981-1985
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
BU/283
McCall, Abner Vernon, 1915-
27 document boxes
BU Records: Chancellor's Office (Abner Vernon McCall) contains records relating to Baylor University's Chancellor from 1981-1985, Judge Abner Vernon McCall. Records include correspondence, reports, and documents concerning Baylor University as well as external organizations McCall had involvement in.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Average.
Biography/Profile
Abner Vernon McCall was born on 1915 June 9 in Perrin, Texas, to parents Gertrude Elizabeth Rhoades McCall and Harry Vernon McCall. At the age of 3, McCall’s father passed away from the flu. After his death, his mother was unable to care for McCall and his siblings, and they were placed in the Masonic School and Home in Fort Worth, Texas. Although not much is known about Abner’s early life at this school, it is well known that Abner flourished academically. Graduating as the Valedictorian of his class, Abner earned the prestigious Masonic Scholarship, providing him the funding to attend Baylor University. Continuing his successes at Baylor, McCall graduated as valedictorian of the Baylor Law Class of 1938.
Entering law practice, McCall remained near Baylor to teach law classes, serving as an assistant professor from 1938 to 1942. He left Baylor for one year to earn a Masters of Law at the University of Michigan. After receiving his degree, he worked with the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) for three years before returning to Baylor. Two years after his return, he was appointed Dean of the Law School. During his time teaching, he was also appointed a Texas Supreme Court Justice in 1956 June by then Governor Allan Shivers.
By 1959, McCall was appointed Executive Vice President of Baylor University. In 1961, McCall was appointed President of Baylor University, a position he held for 21 years. During his tenure at Baylor, he was instrumental in expanding Baylor’s campus, raising the enrollment numbers, and improving the financial conditions of the university. While McCall was president, he continued to teach law courses. In 1981, McCall became the Chancellor of Baylor. He served in this capacity until 1985, then served as President Emeritus.
McCall was known for his traditional Baptist views on social issues pertaining to campus life, including dancing, alcohol, and card playing. He served in many religious organizations in a variety of capacities, including President of the Baptist General Convention of Texas in 1964-1965 and Vice President of the Southern Baptist Convention in 1979-1980. Growing up surrounded by Masons, McCall was also involved in the Masonic Order and was coronated a 33rd degree Scottish Rite Mason in 1969. In 1991, McCall was honored with the Grand Cross, the highest honor granted to a Free Mason.
McCall passed away at the age of 90 on 1995 June 11 and is buried in Oakwood Cemetery in Waco, Texas.
Scope and Content
This collection begins in 1980 and ends in 1988, with some items undated. While this collection mainly encompasses files from Abner McCall's time as Chancellor at Baylor University from June 1981 to June 1985, some folders include materials from McCall's time as President and President Emeritus.
Series I. Internal includes correspondence, reports, and other materials that were produced specifically by Baylor University. This includes departments, organizations, and correspondence topically related to events or issues at Baylor. Series II. External includes correspondence, reports, newsletters, and other materials that were produced outside of Baylor or for institutions outside of Baylor. This includes organizations such as Brazos Higher Education Authority, Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT), Texas System of Natural Laboratories, and many others. Some of these materials are related to McCall and his involvement in external organizations while others deal specifically with his position at Baylor. Series III. People includes correspondence and documents that were organized and filed by a person's last name. Series IV. Personal includes appointment books, personal correspondence, and speeches McCall wrote.
Series II. External is the largest series in the collection. Throughout the entire collection, there are cross reference sheets within folders that direct researchers to other files with similar topics. These cross reference sheets were created and filed by McCall's office staff and were retained during processing. BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall) contains January-May 1981 files and BU Records: President Emeritus' Office (Abner Vernon McCall) contains June-December 1985 files.
Arrangement
Prior to current processing, this collection was housed in labeled folders in no particular order. Original titles were retained where possible and any title information added during processing is noted in brackets in the folder titles.
Currently, the collection is organized in four series: I. Internal, II. External, III. People, IV. Personal. Within all five series, folders are arranged relatively alphabetically and chronological thereafter.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. BU/283. Acquired 1990-10-03
Related Resources
Items in related collections
BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1845-1981, undated, Bulk: 1961-1981
BU Records: President Emeritus' Office (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1857-1995, undated, Bulk: 1985-1995
BU Records: President's Office: Herbert Hal Reynolds
Related references
“Abner Vernon McCall (1915-1995).” Abner Vernon McCall, The University of Texas at Austin. Accessed 2019 December 1.
Find A Grave, Inc. "Abner Vernon McCall." Memorial #15715101. Databases. Accessed 2019 December 1.
Saxon, Wolfgang. “Abner V. McCall, 80, Educator Who Led in Expansion of Baylor.” The New York Times, 1995 June 12.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
McCall, Abner, 1915-
Subjects (Organizations)
Baylor University -- Administration.; Baylor University -- History -- 20th century.; Baylor University -- Records and correspondence.; Baylor University. College of Medicine -- History.
Subjects
Baptist universities and colleges -- Texas -- Waco.
Genres
Annual reports.; Appointment Books.; Business correspondence.; Minutes (Records); Newsletters.; Personal correspondence.; Records (Documents); Speeches.
- Internal, 1981-1985, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Average.
  Biography/Profile
  This series includes correspondence, reports, minutes, and other materials relating to the inner-workings of Baylor. Materials produced specifically for Baylor or by Baylor departments, organizations, and individuals can be found in this series. Some files are restricted due to the existence of personally identifiable information, or based on the current restriction policy governing university archives. This series is in average condition.
  Access Restrictions
  Some folders within this series are restricted due to personally identifiable information, confidentiality, and current laws and policies. These folders are denoted as restricted. Contact an archivist for details.
  - Admissions, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Admissions, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Association, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Association, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Association (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Association (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Association (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Armstrong Browning Library, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Assistant Vice President and Director of Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Department, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Aviation Department, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Chamber of Commerce, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Press, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Baylor University Medical Center, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Book Store, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Champlain, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chemistry Department, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Classics Department, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Communication Studies, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Continuing Education for Church and Denominational Workers, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Crouch Gift, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Dean of Academic Services, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Dean of College of Arts and Sciences, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Denominational and Community Relations, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Development, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Development Council, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - English Department, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - External Affairs, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Development Program and Institute, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fine Arts, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - First Families of Baylor Award, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - General Counsel, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Geology Department, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Dean and Assistant Vice President, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Heritage Club, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - History Department, 1984-1985, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Honors Program, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Inauguration — Reynolds, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - International Students, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Institute for Oral History, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Institute for the Study of the Interaction of Foreign and Domestic Affairs, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - J.M. Studies in Church and State, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Journalism Department, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Law School (1 of 4), 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Law School (2 of 4), 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Law School (3 of 4), 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Law School (4 of 4), 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Moody Memorial Library, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Office of Public Relations, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Oral Communications Department, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Physical Education — Baylor Camp Recreation Center, Recreational Sports, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Political Science, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Profile ’85 Campaign, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Psychology Department, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - School of Education, 1982-1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - School of Music, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Self-Study, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Sociology, Anthropology, Social Work, and Gerontology, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Spanish [Mormon professor], 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Texas Collection, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Treasurer [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - University Committees, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - University Council, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - University Senate, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Vice President for Business Affairs, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Vice President for Business Affairs, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Vice President for External Affairs, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- External, 1980-1985, undated; 2
  This series includes correspondence, reports, minutes, publications, programs, and other materials relating to institutions and organizations outside of Baylor University. Some materials are related to McCall as an individual and his interests and affiliations, while others are directly related to his position as Chancellor. This series is in average condition.
  - Abilene Christian University, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - A.M. Aiken Symposium, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Anti-Crime Council of Texas (ACT), 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Association of Texas Colleges and Universities (ATCU), 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas (BGCT), 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas (BGCT), 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Baptist Laity Journal, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation, 1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (1 of 5), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (2 of 5), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (3 of 5), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (4 of 5), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (5 of 5), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (1 of 3), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (2 of 3), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (3 of 3), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (1 of 4), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (2 of 4), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (3 of 4), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (4 of 4), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Brazos River Authority, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Brown Foundation, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Carr P. Collins Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Citizens National Republic Bank, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cooper Foundation, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Cooper Foundation, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Foundation, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Cooper Foundation (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Cooper Foundation (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cooper Foundation (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Cooper Foundation, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Coordinating Board: Texas College and University System, 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Education Commission, 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Education Commission of the States, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Fanini Ministries, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - First Federal Savings and Loan, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Foundations, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Governor’s Task Force on Higher Education, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Greater Waco Chamber of Commerce, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Heart O’ Texas Council — Boy Scouts of America, 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Horatio Alger Association, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Howard Payne University, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT) (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas (ICUT), 1985, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Little League, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Masonic Home and School of Texas, 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Members of Congress, 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Opal G. Cox Charitable Trust, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - The Philosophical Society of Texas (1 of 2), 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - The Philosophical Society of Texas (2 of 2), 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Right to Work Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Right to Work Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Right to Work Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Right to Work Committee — Board of Directors Business Session, 1985 May 11 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Scottish Rite, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Scottish Rite, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Scottish Rite (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Scottish Rite (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Scottish Rite, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Scottish Rite, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Southern Baptist Convention (1 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Southern Baptist Convention (2 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Southern Baptist Convention, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - SBC Today, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Southern University Conference, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - State Ethics Committee (1 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - State Ethics Committee (2 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - State Ethics Committee (3 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - State Ethics Committee (4 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - State Bar College, 1981-1985 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Texans War on Drugs Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Texas Colleges and Universities Coordinating Board, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Texas Council of Church-Related Colleges, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Texas Independent College Fund, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Texas Independent College Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Texas Judicial Council, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Texas Judicial Council, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Texas Legislative Conference, 1981-1985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (1 of 4), 1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (2 of 4), 1982 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (3 of 4), 1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (4 of 4), 1982 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (1 of 6), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (2 of 6), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (3 of 6), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (4 of 6), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (5 of 6), 1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (6 of 6), 1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Texas System of Natural Laboratories, Inc. (TSNL) (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Texas Utilities Company (1 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Texas Utilities Company (2 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Texas Utilities Company, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Texas Utilities Company, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Tryon Foundation, 1981-1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Waco Business League, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Waco Philosophers Club, 1981-1985 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Wellway Centers, Incorporated (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Wellway Centers, Incorporated (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Wellway Centers, Incorporated, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Welch Foundation, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- People, 1981-1988, undated; 3
  This series includes correspondence and their supporting documents. The series is organized alphabetically by last name. The last name used to organize the files, in some cases, is the name of an individual discussed in the correspondence rather than the correspondent. Any individual with a folder specifically labeled with their name was a folder that was retained from the original order. All other materials were found in miscellaneous folders and put into alphabetical order by last name according to the name written at the top of each piece of paper. This series is in average condition.
  - A — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Allbritton, Joe, 1981-1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - B — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Bobo, Dr. Zach, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - C — Correspondence (1 of 2), 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - C — Correspondence (2 of 2), 1981-1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - D — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Daniel, Governor Bill, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - E — Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - F — Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - G — Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - H — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Hollandsworth, Earl, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Hollandsworth, Earl (1 of 9), 1981-1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Hollandsworth, Earl (2 of 9), 1981-1988 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Hollandsworth, Earl (3 of 9), 1981-1988 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Hollandsworth, Earl (4 of 9), 1981-1988 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Hollandsworth, Earl (5 of 9), 1981-1988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Hollandsworth, Earl (6 of 9), 1981-1988 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Hollandsworth, Earl (7 of 9), 1981-1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Hollandsworth, Earl (8 of 9), 1981-1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Hollandsworth, Earl (9 of 9), 1981-1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - J — Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - K — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - L — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - M — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - N — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - P — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - R — Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - S — Correspondence (1 of 2), 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 1)